traveling to
ional the destruction caused by the
omnic here it reminds me of Home things
can be destroyed but as long as the
people are strong they can always be
rebent I hate to break this to everyone
but if we're here to blow up the Bots
someone's beating us to it
had the strangest dream about this place
there was a witch and a monster and
crazy
right think any of these Taps still work
I'm feeling An Almighty
thirst they used to believe that vites
lived in these Woods ridiculous isn't
it after hearing all of reinhard's
stories I've always wanted to come here
I will reclaim my Master's
armor many of my comrades fell in battle
here may I rest in
peace this is no Castle it's a
[Music]
tomb this is the hometown of my master
balder he was born here would he died
here too much blood was spiled in my
country during the war
we fought a terrible battle here many
Crusaders lost their
lives they killed many of your kind here
[Music]
Bastion I will not let the Fate that
befell this place happen to my country